I was in the countryside, it is eight hours drive, so I made sure that I had to come
because I really honor Holly and the One Love Travel Club, which we have really shared
with them for some time now, and it's a privilege actually to share the great experience that
you have from the other side, bringing it over here and sharing this wonderful life.
Thank you so much.
So, I would like to get to know each other.
You thought she was stuck in the bathroom.
I tried my bathroom.
They use a whiteboard.
It can take up to 30 students, very little ones attend the school.
We don't speak the same language because we have several tribes in Kenya.
When we introduce them to the school learning environment, we bring another language that
we introduce to them.
That is Swahini and then English.
You will find that very many parents, they don't have jobs.
They don't have jobs.
They don't have something to give the kids in the evening.
So, they bring their kids over here.
We really love the kids.
And when they come, they find the kids taken good care of.
They really feel very proud.
I feel very proud.
Mambo!
Papati!
Say cheese!
Cheese!
Say abujubuju!
Abujubuju!
Hi, Vani.
Hello.
This is where the boys sleep.
We have boys in school who don't have somewhere to sleep at home.
When you enter here, you can really feel the learning mood.
You know?
Some of y'all need this.
Just know that people who English is their first language, still struggling.
Still struggling with this crisis.
I think a lot of us often forget, in our own struggles, just how different it is in other
places.
And it is really an honor for us to be able to help in even, you know, the smallest of
ways or in the biggest of ways and know that it truly, I don't know how else to say it,
but it really truly is a blessing for us to be able to be a blessing, you know?
And to see you all have the opportunity to be anything you want to be.
I'm a very big believer that we are each other's business.
You know?
Like that's what I really, really believe.
And I saw a sign in the room and it said, um, ways to be a good citizen.
And I said, this is a, this is a different place because you're not just teaching maths
and you're not just teaching, um, science and reading, but you're teaching spirit and soul.
And so for us to be able to pour into that and for us to be able to see that really lets
us know that this is a beautiful place and we get to be a part of it.
So thank you.
This kind of steak food?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's normal.
Camo?
Camo.
Yeah, yeah.
Say, like, they want to say, don't keep quiet.
Two GLS should need to open up.
Then 21 means we need to understand each other.
Yeah.
Good story.
So I want to say that, uh, we'll meet next time.